For your baby.
To eat.
His Valyrian is terrible.
He only wants to give you money,
so your baby can eat.
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
The Lord of Light sent the
Mother of Dragons to you,
and those who love the
darkness chased her away.
How will you respond?
Will you wring your hands, while you
wait for the Mother of Dragons to return?
Or will you take up her flames yourselves?
Will you fight for your own salvation,
now that Queen Daenerys
is not here to fight for you?
Maybe she saw a ghost.
My friend's mother saw a ghost
and her hair turned white.
Pink people are afraid of the sun.
It burns their skin.
This one stands too long in the sun
and her hair goes white.
You think she's got white pussy hair too?
You ever been with a girl
with white pussy hair?
Only when I was fucking your grandma.
I'll ask Khal Moro for a night with you.
What do you think?
Pretty eyes, but she's an idiot.
She doesn't have to be smart
to get fucked in the ass.
I like to talk when I'm finished.
Otherwise, we might as well be dogs.
For you, my Khal.
The white-haired girl we found in the hills.
Look at those lips, blood of my blood.
Blue-eyed women are witches.
It is known.
Cut off her head, before she
casts a spell on you.
Even if I was blind,
I'd hear my wives say,
"Cut off her head"
and I'd know this woman is beautiful.
I'm glad I'm not blind.
Seeing a beautiful woman naked
for the first time,
what is better than that?
Killing another Khal?
Yes, killing another Khal.
Conquering a city
and taking her people as slaves,
and taking her idols back to Vaes Dothrak.
Breaking a wild horse,
forcing it to submit to your will.
Seeing a beautiful woman
naked for the first time
is among the five best things in life.
Do not touch me.
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of the House Targaryen,
the First of Her Name, the Unburnt,
Queen of Meereen,
Queen of the Andals
and the Rhoynar and the First Men,
Khaleesi of the Great Grass Sea,
Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons.
You are nobody, the millionth of your name,
Queen of Nothing,
slave of Khal Moro.
Tonight I will lie with you,
and if the Great Stallion is kind,
you will give me a son.
Do you understand?
I will not lie with you.
And I will bear no children,
for you, or anyone else.
Not until the sun rises in the west,
and sets in the east.
I told you she was a witch.
Cut off her head.
I like her. She has spirit.
I was wife to Khal Drogo,
son of Khal Bharbo.
Khal Drogo is dead.
I know.
I burnt his body.
Forgive me. I did not know.
It is forbidden to lie with a Khal's widow.
No one will touch you.
You have my word.
If you will escort me back to Meereen,
I will see that your khalasar is given
a thousand horses, as a sign of my gratitude.
When a Khal dies,
there is only one place for his khaleesi.
Vaes Dothrak.
The Temple of the Dosh Khaleen.
To live out her days with the
widows of dead khals.
It is known.